Indoor Wallpaper Pack - Bacco

Thanks for buying my texture pack.

In "Materials" folder you find materials that is ready to be use.
Just apply the material in your scene to use it.

All the textures beeing used is located in "Textures" folder

Tip: Increase the X and Y value of "Tiling" located in the inspector of an material.
That will repeat the textures.

If you have questions or feedback. Contact me at: mail@parlinde.com

Best regards Lindesign